<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/features/</guid><description>Feature set Offline Data Our app is completely offline compatible We have over 30.000 ingredients stored in our data set. It was important for us to guarantee that the user is always able to use the app. Therefore we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to rely on an internet connection.
Text Recognition/Filtering Our app uses the Firebase ML text recognition to recognise the ingredients on the back of the product.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/features/</guid><description>Feedback The main purpose of our application is to get good and constructive feedback to enhance meetings in an agile work environment. A look at the questionnaire Fast and easy To get people to respond on a daily basis this process has to be quick and easy. Therefore we focussed on getting the best possible assessments with only a few clicks.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/features/</guid><description>LEVELS Main Menu room with level picker 3 game levels, each a differently styled town Storyline, one story for each level Tutorial, found in the main menu, in form of a text on a table Score system including highscore, both displayed in each scene Menus (main, pause, victory, game over) Background music, one melody for each level (music not made by us, see Assets at the bottom of this page) Japanese inspired level Medieval inspired level Oriental inspired level Combat Posing Enemy: imitate the enemies’ pose Boxing Enemy: targets to hit and player controllers with matching colors and haptic feedback Final bosses distinguishable by masks fitting each storyline Enemy spawn direction indicator Symbol drawing, as the final part of each fight against an enemy Player health system (enemies fight back) Sounds for: hitting targets, player being hit, enemy sound, firework sounds (sounds not made by us, see Assets at the bottom of this page) Boxing Enemy Posing Enemy Symbol Drawing Interactive Environment Color changing, with color change indicator in the form of fireworks Throwable items: items that you can pick up and throw at the enemy Endless mode, where the enemies keep spawning with an increasing speed Story pieces: small floating pieces of papers, each displaying a part of the current map’s storyline Fitness Aspects Boxing against enemies Squatting to dodge enemy attacks Fast-changing game-pace: fast boxing into drawing into posing and so on.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/features/</guid><description>User roles In our application we have two roles: recruiter and job seeker. The recruiter can create job offers and job seekers can fill out their resume. Simple sign up The user fills out a questionnaire where they answer questions about the job or employee they are looking for. A job seeker answers questions about their own skills, expectations and values.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/features/</guid><description>Our MeshHeadz application has, as already indicated, a broad spectrum of features but is nevertheless designed to be simple and clear.
Create Your Own Projects After first opening the app, users are able to create as many individual projects as they please, to save their photographs and 3D-models in an organized way. Create Your Own Projects Take Photos With The Built In Camera In order to create a 3D-model of their head, users must be able to include photos they have taken in their projects.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/features/</guid><description>User roles In our application we have two roles: recruiter and job seeker. The recruiter can create job offers and job seekers can fill out their resume. Simple sign up The user fills out a questionnaire where they answer questions about the job or employee they are looking for. A job seeker answers questions about their own skills, expectations and values.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/features/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/features/</guid><description>Features List The features listed below are included in the augmented board game &amp;ldquo;The Mole&amp;rdquo;:
Adaptive music Own map design Minigame Occasion fields Game history Clue configurator Clue share system Evidence verification English and German language &amp;ldquo;Intelligent&amp;rdquo; pursuer Traitor in team Token login Rejoin capabilities Debug mode The most important features are explained in the following sections.
Create And Join The Game To create the game, two steps are required.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/features/</guid><description>Athletimize facilitates training planning and management by including holistic data. It provides the following features to athletic teams and organizations:
Assessments We have two types of assessments:
Daily assessments are answered everyday in the morning. The questions range from the athlete&amp;rsquo;s state of mind to their body condition Session assessments are answered right after a training or match has taken place. The athletes give their personal view about the intensity of the session and provide the time that they were involved.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/features/</guid><description>Our models are still being trained. Please revisit us later to view our results.
World Generator To produce a variety of pathfinding situations we created a world generator that can output voxel worlds of any desired size. There are 5 different presets for the Perlin noise based terrain generation. These produce different challenges for the learning process. Noise Canyon Maze Hills Small hills The generator can mass-produce worlds with multiple start and end points and either fixed or random preset types.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/features/</guid><description>Training-related task To provide an ingame objective which represents an everyday work task to the trainees, their instructors were included in the developing process.
When entering the virtual workshop the players receive the task to craft a dice. This requires interaction with cutting machines like the hand lever or the guillotine shears as well as the bench drill to perforate the metal workpieces. To set the final product together, a glue gun needs to be used.</description></item><item><title>Über Uns</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/about-us/</guid><description>v.l.n.r: Adil, Daphna, Florian, John, Diro, Michael Herausforderungen Vor dem Projekt kannten wir uns noch nicht bzw. nur von Sehen her. Aufgrund der besonderen Schwierigkeiten dieses Semesters, konnten wir uns auch nicht persönlich treffen und uns so kennenlernen. Zusätzlich hatte die Hälfte von uns noch nie mit Unity, der Entwicklungsumgebung, mit der wir unser Spiel erstellen wollten, gearbeitet. Doch rückblickend müssen wir sagen, dass die Zusammenarbeit im Projekt trotz alledem sehr harmonisch und produktiv verlief.</description></item><item><title>Ideenfindung</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/idea-finding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/idea-finding/</guid><description>Zu Beginn des Projektes, hatten wir noch keine klare Idee von dem Thema Motorik und Konzentration und wie wir ein dazu passendes Spiel bauen könnten. Deshalb lag unser Fokus am Anfang stark auf der Recherche zu diesem Thema, bevor wir begonnen haben Spieleideen zu sammeln.
Recherche Wir hatten uns bereits früh darauf geeinigt, dass das Spiel auf Smartphones ausgerichtet sein soll. Aus diesem Grund haben wir uns explizit angesehen, was es bereits für Spiele auf diesen Geräten gibt, die in unsere Thematik passen könnten.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/process/</guid><description>First steps Our goal was clear. We generally knew what we had to do to reach our goal. Some questions still came up, that had to be answered first, before starting to code. We had to first decide on a framework we want to use. It was also important to know upfront whether our app is offline or online. After answering all these questions, we split up in two subgroups.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/process/</guid><description>How did we start The first step in our creation process was to identify the needs of Brandung and analyze the market. To our surprise we couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any product that was focusing on meetings the same way we do. We began thinking about our own experiences with meetings or even classes and what kind of tool could have been useful to evaluate them. We came up with a bunch of fancy features but narrowed it down to a core functionality at the end for our MVP:</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/process/</guid><description>Brainstorming This project was initially pitched to us as a VR audio fitness game for the Oculus Quest. While we did have the freedom to come up with any kind of VR game we wanted, we did stick with the idea of a fitness game. In one of our first meetings we tasked everyone to come up with at least one game concept. All ideas were written down in a shared Google Docs document.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/process/</guid><description>Research Benchmarking &amp;amp; Market Research Compared thoroughly the existing hiring platforms on the market and found out the common issues that users faced while using these platforms.
Created surveys with Google Forms to research user experience with different hiring platforms.
User Research Surveys Conducted surveys to assess the important aspects of the employment process and to figure out the right questions to ask in order to find the top match.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/process/</guid><description>Design Thinking Process Ever since our team started working together, we have been integrating the method of Design Thinking - a non-linear, iterative process - to our project work. We went back and forth through its six stages to continuously improve our product. Design Thinking Process First Steps With a few ideas in mind we spent time researching to come up with potential technologies that best suit our goal and planned our next steps.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/process/</guid><description>Research Benchmarking &amp;amp; Market Research Compared thoroughly the existing hiring platforms on the market and found out the common issues that users faced while using these platforms.
Created surveys with Google Forms to research user experience with different hiring platforms.
User Research Surveys Conducted surveys to assess the important aspects of the employment process and to figure out the right questions to ask in order to find the top match.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/process/</guid><description> The development process</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/process/</guid><description>Project goals and approach Our approach towards developing The Mole can be explained with the help of Schell’s Elemental Tetrad [1]. This is a framework for game designers to support them in creating a certain desired gaming experience while keeping the purpose and the dependencies between the four pillars mechanics, aesthetics, story and technology of a game in mind.
To predefine the gaming experience, we followed the given project guideline to create a board game augmented by digital elements.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/process/</guid><description>The development process Throughout the duration of the project, we worked in a &amp;lsquo;Scrum-ban&amp;rsquo; mode. While we did plan our weekly sprints, we also worked very much on a &amp;lsquo;what-is-needed&amp;rsquo; basis. As we all had very different schedules, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have Dailies. Once a week we had a meeting that was Review and Sprint Planning in one. All code was located in a shared Gitlab repository, where we checked in our code whenever a ticket was solved.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/process/</guid><description>Research Due to the lack of machine learning experience we started our project by researching how machine learning works, what different kinds of concepts exist and which of them are relevant for our path finding problem. Our project supervisors provided us with some useful starting points for this.
The main sources we built upon are GAN Path Finder, Pathfinding via Reinforcement and Imitation Multi-Agent Learning and Hands-on machine learning with Scikit-Learn, Keras, and TensorFlow</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/process/</guid><description>Starting off We started this project without any prior experience in the field of occupational safety measures and how they are taught. As the need was brought to us in the context of a larger research project, we scheduled Zoom meetings with educational partners from AVT and bfw. They invited us to visit their workshops in order to gather enough information about the machines being used as well as the potential injuries.</description></item><item><title>Plattform- und Designentscheidung</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/platform-and-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/platform-and-design/</guid><description>Warum für Smartphones? Schon zu Beginn des Projekts hatten wir uns geeinigt, dass unser Spiel für Smartphones ausgelegt sein soll. Der hauptsächliche Grund war, dass wir der Meinung sind, dass wir dadurch sowohl unsere Zielgruppe der jungen Erwachsenen noch besser erreichen können als auch, dass ein Spiel, das Konzentration und Motorik trainieren soll, nicht über mehrere Stunden am Stück unterhalten muss. Wir wollten den Fokus eher auch kurze Aufgaben legen, sodass das Spiel gut zwischendurch, z.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/tech-stack/</guid><description>Our tech stack Tech Stack Flutter™️ The first step of the journey was choosing a framework that meets our requirements. We had very little experience with app development, so it was necessary to do some self-reliant research first and we ended up with two candidates: React Native and Flutter and we decided on the latter. The framework Flutter gained a lot of popularity among App-Developers in recent years.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/tech-stack/</guid><description>Our tech stack Next.js/React The base for app was Next.js and the React library.
Some of the components we used:
axios dotenv express mongoose node-cron nodemon styled-components MongoDB MongoDB serves as our database. We save the feedback in a database and read from it for the evaluation. Azure To access the calendars and user data, we connected our app to Azure / the Microsoft Outlook API.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/tech-stack/</guid><description>Our tech stack Unity &amp;amp; Oculus VR The Project was presented as an Oculus Quest VR Game in Unity from the very beginning - and we were quite happy with these tools. While some of us already had some experience in Unity, we still took our time to get to know the engine properly. Oculus offers an Integration Package for Unity, which helped us to get started with VR development.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/tech-stack/</guid><description>Elasticsearch With Elasticsearch we can retrieve data with customized parameters and it will show us the best results based on our query. EJS EJS is a JavaScript template, which essentially allows us to implement JavaScript into HTML files. Thanks to that we were able to display dynamic content on the pages. MongoDB MongoDB is easy to implement with JS, which made it very attractive to us.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/tech-stack/</guid><description>These are the programming languages, frameworks, libraries and other software products that our application, web service and 3D-pipeline is built on.
Client After detailed research, we decided to develop an Android application using the IDE Android Studio. Our decision to use the programming language Java over Kotlin, was based upon the fact that it is the main language that is taught in our studies.
All data that is generated while using the app is stored directly on the device in folders that were especially created for that.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/tech-stack/</guid><description>Elasticsearch With Elasticsearch we can retrieve data with customized parameters and it will show us the best results based on our query. EJS EJS is a JavaScript template, which essentially allows us to implement JavaScript into HTML files. Thanks to that we were able to display dynamic content on the pages. MongoDB MongoDB is easy to implement with JS, which made it very attractive to us.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/tech-stack/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/tech-stack/</guid><description>Technologies In the following, all important technologies used in our project are indicated. For each technology, the logo, name and general function are presented. This should help you to better understand the graphic of the software architecture in the next paragraph. Architecture The following graphic describes the software architecture of the game &amp;ldquo;The Mole&amp;rdquo;.
There are two basic elements in the architecture, a backend server and a frontend server.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/tech-stack/</guid><description>Tech Stack React &amp;amp; Typescript For our Frontend we decided to use ReactJS with TypeScript. This gave us the advantage of having a well-documented library with a plethora of available resources. React is relatively easy to learn and it allowed us to have a modular structure where we could build various reusable components. To improve and ensure code-quality, we set up very strict linting and formatting rules.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/tech-stack/</guid><description>.nomargin figure{ margin: 0; } Core Technology All machine learning related aspects of our project are built upon Python envionments that were managed with Conda. The reinforcement learning approach uses the TF-Agents library, which is as part of the Tensorflow framework. Our generative adversarial network was created with PyTorch. The machine learning process was accelerated using Nvidia's CUDA toolkit. The training data generation and result visualization was achieved in Unity with C#.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/tech-stack/</guid><description>Development Our prototype was developed in Unity version 2019.4.12f1 and the VRTK version 3.3. We chose these core tools as the group members already had experience developing with them and could apply past knowledge while eliminating learning time. Furthermore, one group member had previously developed scripts for procedural mesh splitting, which became one of the core functions in our program. Modeling Various programs were used for modeling but Blender version 2.</description></item><item><title>Ausblick</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/future-prospects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/future-prospects/</guid><description>Einer der wesentlichen Gründe, warum wir uns schnell auf unser Spielekonzept einigen konnten, war, dass es sehr gut skalierbar ist. Während der Entwicklungsphase sind uns viele weitere Ideen und Elemente eingefallen, mit denen unser Konzept erweitert werden könnte.
So haben wir uns sehr viel mehr Distraktoren ausgedacht, als im fertigen Spiel enthalten sind zusätzlich hatten wir mit anderen Level-Konzepten und Spielmodi experimentiert.
Da wäre zum einen ein Free Play-Modus. Statt von uns erstellten Leveln, werden hier endlos Level mit einem zufälligen Pfad generiert.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b1-kiss/future/</guid><description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? While things like improving the text recognition or speeding up the scanning are ongoing processes, we still have some ideas for new features that will improve the app. One thing that is on our bucket list, is to contact the European Commission because they have shown interest in projects that use their data. The European Commission has other datasets that are related to the CosIng dataset that we use, so we want to expand our dataset and implement relations between these datasets.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b2-feedbackapp/future/</guid><description>Progress over time ⏱ Evaluation timeline Meeting owners already get their respective evaluations for hosted meetings. But, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to see if the received feedback has led to an overall improvement of the meeting quality?
We thought of implementing a view for meeting owners, where they can see their meeting performance over time. The idea was to show a graph or a timeline for a week, month or a specified period.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/future/</guid><description>Future Features Due to the way our Game is built and envisioned, it was quite easy for us to come up with more potential features, than we could actually implement into the game, with the given time, budget and/or skill. Most of the ideas were about adding more variety to the features that were already implemented in the game, such as creating more maps:
For example:</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/future/</guid><description>Here are the features we would have loved to implement if there was more time, of which many were highly requested in the conducted surveys:
More control over matches More matching criterias and filters for the search: To make sure our algorithm works great for personal values, we decided to postpone the implementation of search criterias such as ‘location’ and ‘salary’. We are eager to add them as soon as possible.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/future/</guid><description>Many Ideas, Little Time As it often happens while working on a project, the more time passes, the more ideas come to mind. The same happened to us. In the end, we probably could&amp;rsquo;ve spent many additional months developing our product. Short-term goals In general we think that with more time to develop, we would have become more experienced and therefore more confident in writing efficient code, what would result in our application being faster and the user experience being better.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b5-rematch-project/future/</guid><description>Here are the features we would have loved to implement if there was more time, of which many were highly requested in the conducted surveys:
More control over matches More matching criterias and filters for the search: To make sure our algorithm works great for personal values, we decided to postpone the implementation of search criterias such as ‘location’ and ‘salary’. We are eager to add them as soon as possible.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/future/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m1-augmented-boardgame-experience/future/</guid><description>Accessibility Due to the time constraints of this project, our first and foremost goal was to create a working prototype to present at the end of the semester.
One of the most important next steps, now that we achieved that goal, is to make sure the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines are followed. While some features of the game offer great opportunities, e.g. the logged history of each game for which we could add an voice over for the visually impared, for others we will need the option to disable them if needed.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m2-leistungstracker/future/</guid><description>We focused on building a technically stable and well-architected project that could and will be the foundation for an application that will be used by athletic corporations. Our architecture and tech stack are built so that new features can easily be added.
Future features Advanced session planning (attendance, sickness, etc.) Team communication (chats, comments) Medical information &amp;amp; treatments</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m3-deep-3d-pathfinding/future/</guid><description>What is next? The timespan for this project was only sufficient to train the models for a proof of concept stage. With more time and hyperparameter adjustments the quality of the path predictions could be improved. More Concepts As part of our project we also came up with more concepts which have not yet been implemented.
The first is “step by step walking from both directions”.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/future/</guid><description>Our Future Plans Our team is very focused to keep working on our project in this coming semester.
As far as we have come now it gives us a very good foundation to come forward with our work in our VR application. We hope we can make it even better for users and maybe even provide it for other work fields. One field, which was especially asked for, would e.</description></item><item><title>Videos</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/videos/</guid><description> Präsentation Gameplay Editor</description></item><item><title>Screenshots</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b1-hexarcade/gallery/</guid><description/></item><item><title>App gallery</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/gallery/</guid><description> Main screen of our App Onboarding screen Unit screen Unit multiple choice quiz screen Unit single choice quiz screen Unit fill the blank quiz screen Unit feedback screen Knowledgebase screen Knowledgebase unit screen Profile screen Archievement screen Login screen</description></item><item><title>App gallery</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m3-mobile-image-organization/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m3-mobile-image-organization/gallery/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_fotos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_fotos/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Concept gallery</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/concept/</guid><description> Unhooked wireframe concept</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/contact/</guid><description>The IMIxShowtime is a showcase of the term-long practical projects in the International Media and Computing Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and Master&amp;rsquo;s programmes. It takes place every term on the Friday of the last week of lectures.</description></item><item><title>Das Team</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_dasteam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_dasteam/</guid><description>Unser Team besteht aus 8 Student*innen und 3 Betreuer, 2 davon (Jakob und Fabi) sind auch noch Medieninformatik Studenten an der HTW. Wir sind ein sehr internationales Team mit unterschiedlichen Schwerpunkten und Interessen.
Nataliia Alina Daria Leonie Schwerpunkt: Geolocation/Results Page Kostenrechner/Home Page Kostenrechner/Home Page Front End/Settings Page Egor Justin Minh Cong Schwerpunkt: Design/Storybook Front End/Settings Page Back End/Data Fetching Back End/Data Fetching Fabian Tino Jakob</description></item><item><title>Design</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_design/</guid><description>Die Entwicklung des Design der App ist einer der faszinierendsten Prozesse des gesamten Projekts. Es zeigt einem, wie gut man Farben kombinieren kann, wie man unterschiedlichen Formen fühlt, wie man Objekte auf der Seite zusammenstellen kann usw. Dies ist ein kreativer Prozess, an dem jeder teilnehmen kann, unabhängig davon, welches Wissen er besitzt. Er verbindet und gibt viel zum Nachdenken.
Bei der Entwicklung unseres ersten Designs waren wir kaum beschränkt, sodass wir unserer Kreativität freien Lauf lassen konnten.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/features/</guid><description>Show me your cards! The main features of our tool include creating boards with notes on which you can collect ideas, communicate with each other and find new working groups. We tried to make our tool as user-friendly as possible and reduced unnecessary things so the thought process does not get interrupted. This is why The Missing Tool is so lightweight – you don&amp;rsquo;t even need to create a user account!</description></item><item><title>Finding Ideas &amp; Exploring options</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/findingideas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/findingideas/</guid><description>Creative minds trying to find a clear vision In the beginning of our project, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have a clear product vision yet. We had many ideas in mind, from designing little telepresence games like &amp;ldquo;Who Am I?&amp;rdquo;, a flexible poll tool up to an online-tutoring platform for students.
our brainstorming process As interesting as all of those ideas would have been, the spark has not yet jumped. We had to do another round and really ask ourselves – and our supervisor Barne – what it really is that we want to achieve.</description></item><item><title>Future Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/futurefeatures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/futurefeatures/</guid><description>So, what&amp;rsquo;s next? If we have had more time, we probably would have come up with so much more ideas of what to integrate in The Missing Tool. And we already had some ideas that we would like to be realized in the future – either by us or some other students who will get a chance to work on the tool.
Audiochat We want to give our users the opportunity to chat via audio, as an addition to the chat that is already present.</description></item><item><title>Important Dates</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/dates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/dates/</guid><description>After Showtime is just before the next Showtime - upcoming dates</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/imprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/imprint/</guid><description>Diese Seite präsentiert Praxisprojekte der Studiengänge Internationale Medieninformatik Bachelor und Internationale Medieninformatik Master der HTW Berlin und ergänzt diese Webseiten.
Redaktionelle Verantwortung und verantwortliche Ansprechperson Studiengangssprecher der Studiengänge Internationale Medieninformatik
Prof. Dr. Barne Kleinen
HTW Berlin, Fachbereich 4
Wilhelminenhofstr. 75A
12495 Berlin
barne.kleinen@htw-berlin.de
https://www.htw-berlin.de/impressum/
Telefon: +49 30 5019 - 3499
Urheberschutz und Nutzung Die Urheber räumen Ihnen ganz konkret das Nutzungsrecht ein, sich eine private Kopie für persönliche Zwecke anzufertigen. Nicht berechtigt sind Sie dagegen, die Materialien zu verändern und/oder weiter zu geben oder gar selbst zu veröffentlichen.</description></item><item><title>Our Focus: High Usability to stay in the flow.</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/usercentereddesign/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/usercentereddesign/</guid><description>Whatever you need, whenever you need it We made a huge progress in defining our final product vision when we asked ourselves what the specific use cases for our product were. We wanted to provide a tool that gives you the freedom to do what you need to do at the specific moment to make your group-project work, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t overwhelm you with fancy features that you most likely won&amp;rsquo;t make any use of.</description></item><item><title>Pictures</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b2-vrforfuture/pictures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b2-vrforfuture/pictures/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Es gilt die Datenschutzerklärung der HTW Berlin.
Diese Website verwendet keine Cookies und speichert keine Informationen, die über die üblichen Server-Logs der Webserver unter https://htw-berlin.de/ und https://github.com/ für https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ hinausgehen.</description></item><item><title>Product Vision</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/productvision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/productvision/</guid><description>Group projects in no time &amp;hellip; After several weeks of defining and shaping our ideas, we came up with our final vision: A tool that makes it possible for students to brainstorm ideas on notes that can be used on a digital whiteboard, to communicate in real-time about the delevoped ideas and to easily form new sub-groups without the trouble of joining new breakout-rooms.
&amp;hellip; and with no effort at all.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/projects/</guid><description>This term there are 6 bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and 4 master&amp;rsquo;s projects.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/schedule/</guid><description>There will be brief project presentations with a quick Q&amp;amp;A in the morning (very brief presentations, the odd times are real, we might even be a bit quicker than this) and a project fair in the afternoon, both a Zoom Session with various breakout rooms.
Please install the Zoom client to be able to move freely between breakout rooms. Additionally, we have a discord server for announcements, discussions and a general overview independent of the Zoom rooms.</description></item><item><title>Source Code</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/source-code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/source-code/</guid><description>The source code for the frontend and backend is available at GitLab.
Frontend: Gitlab frontend source code
Backend: Gitlab backend source code</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack &amp; Development Tools</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/techstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/techstack/</guid><description>Node.js &amp;amp; Socket.io We made use of Node.js, which is an asynchronous event-driven JavaScript runtime and designed to build scalable network applications. Together with Socket.io, which enables real-time, bidirectional and event-based communication, we had the perfect base for building our application.
MongoDB We decided to work with MongoDb, which is a document-oriented database system, classified as a NoSQL database program. It is really simple to use, but offers deep query-abilities at the same time.</description></item><item><title>Tech-Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_techstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_techstack/</guid><description>Flutter/Dart Das Projekt war das Ergebnis eines Hackathons. Es wurde ursprünglich in Flutter (Dart) geschrieben, also mussten wir nicht die Programmiersprache auswählen, in der wir unsere App schreiben würden, als wir anfingen, daran zu arbeiten. Flutter ist eine sehr einfaches, klares und angenehmes Open-Source UI-Entwicklungs-Kit von Google, die für jeden Anfänger, der sich für die Entwicklung von Cross-Plattform-Apps interessiert, verständlich ist. Alle Komponenten in Flutter sind widgets, aus denen wir unsere App Stück für Stück zusammenstellen.</description></item><item><title>Video</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b4-energy-matters/video/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b4-energy-matters/video/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Videos</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b2-vrforfuture/videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b2-vrforfuture/videos/</guid><description>Preview Presentation</description></item><item><title>Videos</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/bachelor/b3-private-investors/_videos/</guid><description>Wie das Projekt entstanden ist? Arbeit in Corona-Zeiten App für Privatinvestoren Start your Search</description></item><item><title>Videos</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss20/master/m1-unhooked/videos/</guid><description> Showtime presentation</description></item></channel></rss>