<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gefahr erkannt, Gefahr gebannt on IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/</link><description>Recent content in Gefahr erkannt, Gefahr gebannt on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/features/</guid><description>Hier könnte jetzt eine kurze Einleitung zu der Features-Seite stehen. Ich übe mich hier jedoch stattdessen etwas im Creative Writing und erfinde einen Beispiel-Text, damit die Template-Seite nicht komplett leer ist, sondern schon ein bisschen Inhalt enthält. Die einzelnen Features könnten dann so ähnlich wie die untenstehenden Platzhalter auf der Seite präsentiert werden :)
Projects List The projects list provides an overview over all the projects of the current semester.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/process/</guid><description>The development process Jujubes liquorice marshmallow candy sugar plum tiramisu. Wafer icing danish donut. Bonbon macaroon pastry brownie tiramisu gingerbread tart. Tiramisu jelly-o chocolate lemon drops pie sweet roll donut marzipan. Cotton candy brownie macaroon marshmallow candy. Bonbon croissant liquorice cookie. Marzipan apple pie candy croissant. Candy canes bear claw chocolate marzipan topping. Marshmallow topping sugar plum. Sweet roll pudding bear claw. Biscuit apple pie chocolate bar jelly candy canes liquorice.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/tech-stack/</guid><description>Our tech stack Hugo Static Page generator Jujubes liquorice marshmallow candy sugar plum tiramisu. Wafer icing danish donut. Bonbon macaroon pastry brownie tiramisu gingerbread tart. Tiramisu jelly-o chocolate lemon drops pie sweet roll donut marzipan. Cotton candy brownie macaroon marshmallow candy. Bonbon croissant liquorice cookie. Marzipan apple pie candy croissant. Candy canes bear claw chocolate marzipan topping. Marshmallow topping sugar plum. Sweet roll pudding bear claw.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/future/</guid><description>Some intro text without heading. Wafer icing danish donut. Bonbon macaroon pastry brownie tiramisu gingerbread tart. Tiramisu jelly-o chocolate lemon drops pie sweet roll donut marzipan. Cotton candy brownie macaroon marshmallow candy. Bonbon croissant liquorice cookie. Marzipan apple pie candy croissant. Candy canes bear claw chocolate marzipan topping. Marshmallow topping sugar plum. Sweet roll pudding bear claw. Biscuit apple pie chocolate bar jelly candy canes liquorice. Sesame snaps gummi bears cake.</description></item></channel></rss>