<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bachelorprojecttemplate on IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/</link><description>Recent content in Bachelorprojecttemplate on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/features/</guid><description>Feature set Map and Tracking One of the key features of our App is the possibility to pin-point your location and track every move while you&amp;rsquo;re on a stroll out in the wild. With that information, we are creating a Map with the path and pictures you’ve taken along your adventures outside.
Camera and Photo Editor Next up is our Photo Editor.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/process/</guid><description>Idea Jonas
The idea for our app originated out of a conversation with a local gardening project. It is an approach to a rather recent question: How do you make spending time in nature more appealing to children and adolescents who grew up on smartphones and other mobile devices?
Our supervisor, Prof. Dr. Lenz approached us with his initial idea for a mobile application which already laid out most of the core features that the final version of Strollr incorporates, like the ability to take photos and visualize walks with a map.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/tech-stack/</guid><description>Communication Discord During our time developing Strollr, Discord was the main hub for all our conversations, quick questions, short meetups as well as a medium for exchanging pictures and sharing links or useful information.
communication tech stack Zoom Development Notion antonia
During the early planning stages, we decided that our application should be able to run on both Android and iOS.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/bachelor/b3/future/</guid><description> So, what&amp;#39;s next? Anastasiia Mobile Access Additional Features and additional Features Jonas</description></item></channel></rss>