<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Template Project on IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/</link><description>Recent content in Template Project on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/features/</guid><description>Dive into your software. Describe its features with screenshots, graphics and videos or maybe explain essential algorithms via code snippets. What are the strengths of your App? Sell your product.
A Nice Feature A wonderful serenity has taken possession of my entire soul, like these sweet mornings of spring which I enjoy with my whole heart. I am alone, and feel the charm of existence in this spot, which was created for the bliss of souls like mine.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/process/</guid><description>The development process Jujubes liquorice marshmallow candy sugar plum tiramisu. Wafer icing danish donut. Bonbon macaroon pastry brownie tiramisu gingerbread tart. Tiramisu jelly-o chocolate lemon drops pie sweet roll donut marzipan. Cotton candy brownie macaroon marshmallow candy. Bonbon croissant liquorice cookie. Marzipan apple pie candy croissant. Candy canes bear claw chocolate marzipan topping. Marshmallow topping sugar plum. Sweet roll pudding bear claw. Biscuit apple pie chocolate bar jelly candy canes liquorice.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/tech-stack/</guid><description>Our tech stack Hugo Static Page generator Jujubes liquorice marshmallow candy sugar plum tiramisu. Wafer icing danish donut. Bonbon macaroon pastry brownie tiramisu gingerbread tart. Tiramisu jelly-o chocolate lemon drops pie sweet roll donut marzipan. Cotton candy brownie macaroon marshmallow candy. Bonbon croissant liquorice cookie. Marzipan apple pie candy croissant. Candy canes bear claw chocolate marzipan topping. Marshmallow topping sugar plum. Sweet roll pudding bear claw.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b0-template-project/future/</guid><description>Some intro text without heading. Wafer icing danish donut. Bonbon macaroon pastry brownie tiramisu gingerbread tart. Tiramisu jelly-o chocolate lemon drops pie sweet roll donut marzipan. Cotton candy brownie macaroon marshmallow candy. Bonbon croissant liquorice cookie. Marzipan apple pie candy croissant. Candy canes bear claw chocolate marzipan topping. Marshmallow topping sugar plum. Sweet roll pudding bear claw. Biscuit apple pie chocolate bar jelly candy canes liquorice. Sesame snaps gummi bears cake.</description></item></channel></rss>