<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GeZuMi on IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/</link><description>Recent content in GeZuMi on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/features/</guid><description>GeZuMi Game Screens Feature set Player Profile To help players understand which of the &amp;lsquo;player-dots&amp;rsquo; they represent on the game screen and to enable hosts to consciously build teams, all users are asked to provide a player name on the landing page of the app (see first screen in the first row).
Game Setup The first row of the &amp;lsquo;GeZuMi Game Screens&amp;rsquo; figure shows the process of setting up a game that each host will go through.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/process/</guid><description>Workflow The development process was split into one-week sprints, with a self-contained feature release and briefing with the project supervisor every other week. In weekly sprint meetings headed all team members were brought up to date and new goals were set for the upcoming sprint.
For pair programming, brainstorming or researching the team met in smaller sub-groups based on who was working on the respective task. To improve collaboration as a team and reflect on conflicts and impediments, a retrospective was organized whenever the need arose.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/tech-stack/</guid><description>Technology and Software used for the development of GeZuMi Tech Stack Android &amp;amp; Kotlin Android is an open-source, Linux-based OS, mainly developed by Google. It&amp;rsquo;s well-documented and, next to iOsS, the most common operating system for mobile devices. The team decided to develop an Android App, as some existing experience could be extended and most members were Android-device users.
Kotlin is a fairly modern programming language inspired by Java.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ss21/master/m1-gezumi/future/</guid><description>What&amp;#39;s next? GeZuMi can be seen as a Proof of Concept. The goal was to determine whether distances could be reliably calculated and then further processed with Bluetooth technologies. Overall, there are technical limitations to the Bluetooth concept and it is not perfect for determining real time locations.
To reliably work with the transmitted data, the filtering of the RSSI values would have to become more precise so that the unexpected spikes and drops of the values could be balanced out.</description></item></channel></rss>