<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A Spirit Tale on IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/</link><description>Recent content in A Spirit Tale on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Team</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/the-team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/the-team/</guid><description>The Team The “A Spirit Tale” team benefits from a wide diversity across categories, such as semester, age and culture. For this project, we all came together and poured our passion for games and VR into it.
At the very beginning each of us stated what kind of tasks they were interested in working on, which we then used as a guideline, while distributing our tasks. Bartholomäus, Marie and Pauline mainly worked on game programming, while Juri, Nima and Nuri focused on game design/art.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/process/</guid><description>Brainstorming This project was pitched to us as a vr audio fitness game for the Oculus Quest. While we did have the freedom to come up with any kind of vr game we wanted, we did stick with the idea of a fitness game. In one of our first meetings we tasked everyone to come up with at least one game concept. All ideas were written down in a shared Google Docs document.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/tech-stack/</guid><description>Our tech stack Unity &amp;amp; Oculus VR The Project was presented as an Oculus Quest VR Game in Unity from the very beginning - and we were quite happy with these tools. While some of us already had some experience in Unity, we still took our time to get to know the engine properly. Oculus offers an Integration Package for Unity, which helped us to get started with VR development.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws20/bachelor/b3-a-spirit-tale/future/</guid><description>Future features Due to the way our Game is built and envisioned, it was quite easy for us to come up with more potential features, than we could actually implement into the game, with the given time, budget and/or skill. Most of the ideas were about adding more variety to the features that were already implemented in the game, such as creating more maps:
For example:</description></item></channel></rss>