<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A Better Spotify on IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/</link><description>Recent content in A Better Spotify on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/features/</guid><description>The Startpage One of the most important features which is also our unique selling point is our improved Homepage. Web Spotify’s Homepage is filled with content the user doesn’t need or doesn’t want on there. Instead of being greeted with the features and information, they do want, the user has to scroll a lot and doesn’t have the chance to customize it to their needs.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/process/</guid><description>Research Like all projects, Better Spotify started with a lot of research. This entailed not only researching different ideas on how to add new things to the already existing version of Spotify but also researching current trends when it came to the design of music players and Websites in general.
Draft of the process Luckily we didn’t have to come up with an idea to what exactly the project was going to be, but we still needed to figure out in which direction we wanted to go, whether or not we wanted to focus on certain things, recreate Spotify in an entirely different way, focus on a specific age group and so on.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/tech-stack/</guid><description>Backend NodeJS A Javascript runtime used in the backend ExpressJS A backend web application framework for NodeJS Both of these were used for connecting the Spotify API with our own backend and providing the proper information needed to Better Spotify Deployment Heroku Heroku was used for the Deployment of Better Spotify due to the fact that the HTW Server wasn’t enough for our purposes and the Deployment process on Heroku was much simpler and easier to use which made deployment and processing everything a lot faster and better, long term.</description></item><item><title>Future</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/future/</guid><description>Outlook As Better Spotify is an application that was created solely in order to provide an improved version as an already existing streaming platform, the possible extensions to it are truly endless. In order to give a short idea of what had been planned by the team but discarded due to the time restrictions, only a selected few of the 30+ ideas in the backlog will be explained.</description></item></channel></rss>